Forget it. It's too risky.
I'm through doing that shit.
You always say that.
The same thing every time.
"I'm through, never again,
too dangerous."
I know that's what I always say.
I'm always right too.
- You forget about it in a day or two.
- The days of me forgetting are over.
The days of me remembering
have just begun.
You know, when you go on like this,
what you sound like?
- I sound like a sensible fuckin' man.
- You sound like a duck.
- Quack, quack, quack.
- Take heart, 'cause you're never
gonna have to hear it again.
Since I'm never gonna
do it again, you're never
gonna have to hear me quack.
- After tonight?
- Correct. I got all tonight to quack.
- Can I get anyone more coffee?
- Oh, yes!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I mean, the way it is now,
you're takin' the same risk
as when you rob a bank.
Takin' more of a risk.
Banks are easier.
Federal banks ain't supposed to stop you
in any way during a robbery.
They're insured. Why should
they give a fuck? I don't even
need a gun in a Federal bank.
Heard about this one bloke, he walks
into a bank with a portable phone.
He gives the phone to a teller.
The bloke on the other end says,
"We got this guy's little girl.
If you don't give him all your
money, we're gonna kill her."
- Did it work?
- Fuckin' right it worked.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Knucklehead walks into a bank
with a telephone. Not a pistol,
not a shotgun, a fuckin' phone.
- Cleans the place out.
They don't lift a fuckin' finger.
- Did they hurt the little girl?
There probably never was
a little girl. The point of
the story isn't a little girl.
The point of the story is they
robbed a bank with a telephone.
- You want to rob banks?
- I'm not saying I wanna rob banks.
I'm illustrating if we did, it'd be
easier than what we've been doing.
-No more liquor stores?
-What've we been talkin' about?
Yeah, no more liquor stores.
Besides, it ain't the giggle
it used to be. There's too many
foreigners own liquor stores.
Vietnamese, Koreans,
don't even speak fuckin' English.
You tell'em empty out
the register, they don't know
what you're talkin' about.
They make it too personal.
- We keep on, one of these gook
fuckers gonna make us kill him.
- I'm not gonna kill anybody.
I don't want to either.
But they'll probably put us
in a situation where it's us or them.
And if it's not the gooks,
it's these old fuckin' Jews who've owned
the store for 15 fucking generations.
You got Grandpa Irving sitting
behind the counter with
a fucking Magnum in his hand.
Try walkin' into one of those places
with nothing but a phone.
See how far that gets you.
Forget it.
- We're out of it.
- Well, what then, day jobs?
- Not in this life.
- What then?
Garçon, coffee!
This place.
Garçon means boy.
This place?
A coffee shop?
What's wrong with that?
Nobody ever robs restaurants.
Why not?
Bars, liquor stores,
gas stations; you get your head
blown off stickin' up one of them.
Restaurants, on the other hand,
you catch with their pants down.
They're not expectin' to get robbed.
Not as expectin' anyway.
- I bet you could cut down on the
hero factor in a place like this.
- Correct.
Same as banks,
these places are insured.
Manager.
He don't give a fuck.
They're just trying to get you out
before you start pluggin' the diners.
Waitresses. Fuckin' forget it.
No way they're takin' a bullet
for the register.
Busboys. Some wetback gettin'
paid $1.50 an hour...
really give a fuck
you're stealin' from the owner?
Customers sittin' there
with food in their mouths,
they don't know what's goin' on.
One minute, they're havin'
a Denver omelet, the next, someone
is stickin' a gun in their face.
See, I got the idea the last
liquor store we stuck up, remember?
- All the customers kept comin' in.
- Yeah.
You got the idea
of takin' their wallets.
Now, that was a good idea.
- Thank you.
- Made more from the wallets
than we did from the register.
- Yes, we did.
- A lot of people come to restaurants.
- A lot of wallets.
- Pretty smart, huh?
Pretty smart.
I'm ready. Let's do it.
Right now, right here.
- Come on.
- All right. Same as
last time, remember?
You're crowd control.
I'll handle the employees.
- I love you, Pumpkin.
- I love you, Honey Bunny.
Everybody be cool!
This is a robbery!
Any of you fucking pricks move,
and I'll execute
every motherfuckin' last one of you.